Wauregan and Quinebaug Company Records 1981.0010
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series VI: Labor Records, 1855-1958
  - Subseries C: Personnel Files, 1936-1958
    - Deloge, Alice A. P., 1942 (Box 213, Folder 2097)
    - Deloge, Alphonse, 1957 (Box 213, Folder 2098)
    - Deloge, Clement, 1938 (Box 213, Folder 2099)
    - Deloge, Corinne V., 1940 (Box 213, Folder 2100)
    - Deloge, David, 1938 (Box 213, Folder 2101)
    - Deloge, Emile J., 1952 (Box 213, Folder 2102)
    - Deloge, Eva B., 1937 (Box 213, Folder 2103)
    - Deloge, Florence Mandeville, 1941 (Box 213, Folder 2104)
    - Deloge, Frederic, 1938 (Box 213, Folder 2105)
    - Deloge, Louis A., 1940 (Box 213, Folder 2106)
    - Deloge, Maurice J., 1942 (Box 213, Folder 2107)
    - Deloge, Omer N., 1947 (Box 213, Folder 2108)
    - Deloge, Paul, 1943 (Box 213, Folder 2109)
    - Deloge, Rachel, 1942 (Box 213, Folder 2110)
    - Deloge, Raymond, 1951 (Box 213, Folder 2111)
    - Delorge, Dennis, 1942 (Box 213, Folder 2112)
    - Demaine, Lillian, 1949 (Box 214, Folder 2113)
    - DeMello, Antone, 1940 (Box 214, Folder 2114)
    - Demers, Gerard, 1955 (Box 214, Folder 2115)
    - Demers, Germaine, 1956 (Box 214, Folder 2116)
    - Demers, Irene, 1956 (Box 214, Folder 2117)
    - Demoranville, Donald, Jr., 1955 (Box 214, Folder 2118)
    - Demoranville, Elizabeth, 1944 (Box 214, Folder 2119)
    - Demuth, Armand D., 1938 (Box 214, Folder 2120)
    - Demuth, Roland, 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2121)
    - Dennis, Don, 1955 (Box 214, Folder 2122)
    - Denomme, Cecile M., 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2123)
    - Denomme, Joseph C., 1937 (Box 214, Folder 2124)
    - Denomme, Leonel J., 1937 (Box 214, Folder 2125)
    - Denomme, Mary, 1951 (Box 214, Folder 2126)
    - Denomme, Regina B., 1942 (Box 214, Folder 2127)
    - Denomme, Robert, 1956 (Box 214, Folder 2128)
    - Deojay, Ray L., 1952 (Box 214, Folder 2129)
    - Deotte, Raymond, 1955 (Box 214, Folder 2130)
    - Deotte, Richard, 1955 (Box 214, Folder 2131)
    - Despatie, Clement, 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2132)
    - Deroko, John, 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2133)
    - Deroko, Joseph, 1957 (Box 214, Folder 2134)
    - Deroko, Rosanna T., 1940 (Box 214, Folder 2135)
    - Derosier, Gladys G., 1940 (Box 214, Folder 2136)
    - Derosier, Jeannette B. D., 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2137)
    - Derosier, Joseph A., 1938 (Box 214, Folder 2138)
    - Derosier, Leon J., 1948 (Box 214, Folder 2139)
    - Derosier, Pearl, 1957 (Box 214, Folder 2140)
    - Desaulnier, Alexander, 1947 (Box 214, Folder 2141)
    - Desaulnier, David L., 1952 (Box 214, Folder 2142)
    - Desaulniers, Francois X., 1951 (Box 214, Folder 2143)
    - Desaulniers, Marie, 1947 (Box 214, Folder 2144)
    - Desautels, Anita D., 1949 (Box 214, Folder 2145)
    - Desautels, Blanche, 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2146)
    - Desautels, Gerard, 1942 (Box 214, Folder 2147)
    - Desautels, Gerard L., 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2148)
    - Desautels, Jeanne, 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2149)
    - Desautels, John R., 1952 (Box 214, Folder 2150)
    - Desautels, Ovila, 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2151)
    - Deschenes, John, 1940 (Box 214, Folder 2152)
    - Deschenes, Joseph L., 1950 (Box 214, Folder 2153)
    - Deschenes, Roland L., 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2154)
    - Desilets, Andre, 1944 (Box 214, Folder 2155)
    - Desilets, Anna, 1952 (Box 214, Folder 2156)
    - Desilets, George, 1955 (Box 214, Folder 2157)
    - Desilets, Henri S., 1950 (Box 214, Folder 2158)
    - Desilets, John, 1954 (Box 214, Folder 2159)
    - Desilets, Lucien, 1950 (Box 214, Folder 2160)
    - Desilets, Nellie Blanche, 1954 (Box 214, Folder 2161)
    - Desilets, Theresa, 1957 (Box 214, Folder 2162)
    - Desilets, Wesley L., 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2163)
    - Desilets, Wilfred R., 1956 (Box 214, Folder 2164)
    - Desillier, Arthur J., 1940 (Box 214, Folder 2165)
    - Desjardin, Henry, 1955 (Box 214, Folder 2166)
    - Desjardin, Henry, 1947 (Box 214, Folder 2167)
    - Desjardin, Rachel, 1937 (Box 214, Folder 2168)
    - Desjardin, Raymond, 1937 (Box 214, Folder 2169)
    - Desjardin, Roger, 1949 (Box 214, Folder 2170)
    - Desjardin, Yvette M., 1947 (Box 214, Folder 2171)
    - Desjardin, Yvonne, 1947 (Box 214, Folder 2172)
    - Desjardins, Edgar L., 1940 (Box 214, Folder 2173)
    - Desjardins, Ernest D., 1939 (Box 214, Folder 2174)
    - Desjardins, Evelyne Magnam, 1944 (Box 214, Folder 2175)
    - Desjardins, Flora B., 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2176)
    - Desjardins, Francis, 1937 (Box 214, Folder 2177)
    - Desjardins, Louis M., 1939 (Box 214, Folder 2178)
    - Desmarais, Rose M., 1937 (Box 214, Folder 2179)
    - Desorcy, Joseph P., 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2180)
    - Desorcy, Marie B. D., 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2181)
    - Despathy, Norma, 1945 (Box 214, Folder 2182)
    - Despathy, Rose L., 1943 (Box 214, Folder 2183)
    - Despatie, Delphis, 1939 (Box 214, Folder 2184)
    - Despatie, Gerard F., 1952 (Box 214, Folder 2185)
    - Despatie, Frank, 1937 (Box 214, Folder 2186)
    - Despatie, Wilfred, 1945 (Box 214, Folder 2187)
    - Desroches, Benjamin J., 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2188)
    - Desroches, Rita, 1946 (Box 214, Folder 2189)
    - Desrosiers, William, 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2190)
    - Dessert, Amedie, Jr., 1954 (Box 214, Folder 2191)
    - Dessert, Clara L., 1937 (Box 214, Folder 2192)
    - Dessert, Constance G. Levesque, 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2193)
    - Dessert, Dona J., 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2194)
    - Dessert, James, 1946 (Box 214, Folder 2195)
    - Dessert, Leo, 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2196)
    - Dessert, Omer J., 1945 (Box 214, Folder 2197)
    - Dessert, Oscar, 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2198)
    - Deveau, Jeanne B., 1950 (Box 214, Folder 2199)
    - Deveau, Lorraine, 1954 (Box 214, Folder 2200)
    - Devillez, Leon R., 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2201)
    - Devillez, Leon Joseph, 1954 (Box 214, Folder 2202)
    - Devillez, Irene, 1951 (Box 214, Folder 2203)
    - DeVillez, Arthur J., 1943 (Box 214, Folder 2204)
    - Devillez, Eugene S., 1939 (Box 214, Folder 2205)
    - Deviney, Libbie P., 1956 (Box 214, Folder 2206)
    - Deviney, Walter Ernest, Jr., 1943 (Box 214, Folder 2207)
    - Devoe, Irene T., 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2208)
    - Devolve, Earl, 1956 (Box 214, Folder 2209)
    - Devozza, Thomas, 1946 (Box 214, Folder 2210)
    - DeVries, Arline L. Murray, 1949 (Box 214, Folder 2211)
    - Dewhirst, Berrick, 1954 (Box 214, Folder 2212)
    - Dick, Robert, 1951 (Box 214, Folder 2213)
    - Dietz, Charles, 1943 (Box 214, Folder 2214)
    - Dillon, Wilfred, 1940 (Box 214, Folder 2215)
    - Dion, Alphonse B., 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2216)
    - Dion, Arsene, 140 (Box 214, Folder 2217)
    - Dion, Aurele L., Jr., 1954 (Box 214, Folder 2218)
    - Dion, Aurore, 1952 (Box 214, Folder 2219)
    - Dion, Edith T. Courcy, 1952 (Box 214, Folder 2220)
    - Dion, George, 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2221)
    - Dion, John (Jean), 1952 (Box 214, Folder 2222)
    - Dion, Rene, 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2233)
    - Dion, Romain M., 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2224)
    - Dion, Rose P., 1952 (Box 214, Folder 2225)
    - Dion, Rudolphe, 1937 (Box 214, Folder 2226)
    - Dion, Theophile, 1939 (Box 214, Folder 2227)
    - Dion, Yvonne, 1954 (Box 214, Folder 2228)
    - Di Piro, Mary, 1949 (Box 214, Folder 2229)
    - Disciullo, William, 1948 (Box 214, Folder 2230)
    - Dispennett, Eva L., 1939 (Box 214, Folder 2231)
    - DiTullio, Betty, 1948 (Box 214, Folder 2232)
    - DiTullio, Joseph, 1954 (Box 214, Folder 2233)
    - Dixon, James G., 1938 (Box 214, Folder 2234)
    - Dobolek, Joseph, 1942 (Box 214, Folder 2235)
    - Dobrowolsky, Konstanty, 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2236)
    - Doherty, Cornelius, 1946 (Box 214, Folder 2237)
    - Dojka, Salomea, 1956 (Box 214, Folder 2238)
    - Dombek, Pauline L. G., 1942 (Box 214, Folder 2239)
    - Dombek, Walter Joseph, 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2240)
    - Donais, Lillian, 1955 (Box 214, Folder 2241)
    - Donovan, Celina, 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2242)
    - Dore, Mary E. B., 1942 (Box 214, Folder 2243)
    - Dorflinger, Fritz, 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2244)
    - Dorman, Albert V., 19 (Box 214, Folder 2245)
    - Dorman, Exelia C., 1951 (Box 214, Folder 2246)
    - Douglas, Edna M., 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2247)
    - Douglas, Warren C., 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2248)
    - Dow, Farland, 1953 (Box 214, Folder 2249)
    - Downes, George Murray, 1943 (Box 214, Folder 2250)
    - Downes, george R., 1942 (Box 214, Folder 2251)
    - Downing, Maude, 1943 (Box 214, Folder 2252)
    - Doyle, Albert L., 1939 (Box 214, Folder 2253)
    - Doyle, Donald J., 1942 (Box 214, Folder 2254)
    - Doyle, Edmond, 1941 (Box 214, Folder 2255)
    - Doyle, Francis J., 1951 (Box 214, Folder 2256)
    - Doyle, Jean Gilbert, 1947 (Box 214, Folder 2257)
    - Doyle, Lawrence, 1943 (Box 214, Folder 2258)
    - Doyle, Leon, 1947 (Box 214, Folder 2259)
    - Doyle, Lillian G., 1942 (Box 214, Folder 2260)
    - Doyle, Raymond J., 1942 (Box 214, Folder 2261)
    - Doyle, Theona, 1942 (Box 214, Folder 2262)
    - Doyon, Lorraine V., 1951 (Box 214, Folder 2263)
    - Dragon, Annette, 1946 (Box 215, Folder 2264)
    - Dragon, clarence J., Jr., 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2265)
    - Dragon, Clarinda, 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2266)
    - Dragon, Frederick, 1953 (Box 215, Folder 2267)
    - Dragon, Patricia, 1956 (Box 215, Folder 2268)
    - Dragon, Sylvia A., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2269)
    - Dragon, Wilfred E., 1957 (Box 215, Folder 2270)
    - Drapich, Pero, 1947 (Box 215, Folder 2271)
    - Drisco, Clifford A., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2272)
    - Drobiak, Joseph, 1953 (Box 215, Folder 2273)
    - Dropo, Milton, 1941 (Box 215, Folder 2274)
    - Dropo, Walter, 1941 (Box 215, Folder 2275)
    - Dropo, Savo, 1949 (Box 215, Folder 2276)
    - Dropo, Zurka, 1950 (Box 215, Folder 2278)
    - Drunak, John, 1939 (Box 215, Folder 2279)
    - Dube, Raymond E., 1940 (Box 215, Folder 2280)
    - Dubeau, David, 1955 (Box 215, Folder 2281)
    - Dubiel, Joseph, 1953 (Box 215, Folder 2282)
    - Dubiel, Sophie Z., 1941 (Box 215, Folder 2283)
    - Dubois, Albida D., 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2284)
    - Dubysey, Henry, 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2285)
    - Ducat, Leroy W., 1953 (Box 215, Folder 2286)
    - Ducharme, Donat N., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2287)
    - Ducharme, Ernest, 1941 (Box 215, Folder 2288)
    - Ducharme, Marie A., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2289)
    - Ducharme, Marie J., 1938 (Box 215, Folder 2290)
    - Ducharme, Philip L., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2291)
    - Ducharme, Wilfred A., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2292)
    - Ducharme, Yvette, 1956 (Box 215, Folder 2293)
    - Duchesne, Joseph, 1957 (Box 215, Folder 2294)
    - Duchesne, Leo, 1955 (Box 215, Folder 2295)
    - Dudek, Cecile Dessert, 1951 (Box 215, Folder 2296)
    - Dufault, Bernest A., 1953 (Box 215, Folder 2297)
    - Dufault, Edward, 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2298)
    - Dufault, Kenneth, 1956 (Box 215, Folder 2299)
    - Dufault, Marie, 1945 (Box 215, Folder 2300)
    - Dufault, Napoleon, 1939 (Box 215, Folder 2301)
    - Dufault, Norman J., 1947 (Box 215, Folder 2302)
    - Dufault, Rita, 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2303)
    - Dufault, Robert, Jr., 1946 (Box 215, Folder 2304)
    - Dufficy, Eugene P., 1947 (Box 215, Folder 2305)
    - Dufresne, Joseph, 1955 (Box 215, Folder 2306)
    - Dufresne, Marie, 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2307)
    - Dugas, Evelyn G., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2308)
    - Dugas, Marie L., 1940 (Box 215, Folder 2309)
    - Dumaine, Marie E., 1955 (Box 215, Folder 2310)
    - Dumaine, Raymond, 1952 (Box 215, Folder 2311)
    - Dumais, Adolphe, 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2312)
    - Dumas, Delphis N., 1953 (Box 215, Folder 2313)
    - Dumas, Delphis, Jr., 1953 (Box 215, Folder 2314)
    - Dumas, Henry, Jr., 1947 (Box 215, Folder 2315)
    - Dumas, Jean, 1951 (Box 215, Folder 2316)
    - Dumas, Joseph, 1956 (Box 215, Folder 2317)
    - Dumas, Joseph E., 1949 (Box 215, Folder 2318)
    - Dumas, Joseph R., 1954 (Box 215, Folder 2319)
    - dumas, Julia, 1939 (Box 215, Folder 2320)
    - Dumas, Regina B. P., 1940 (Box 215, Folder 2321)
    - Dumont, Cedulie N., 1945 (Box 215, Folder 2322)
    - Dupere, Charles, 1938 (Box 215, Folder 2323)
    - Dupere, Claudina J., 1940 (Box 215, Folder 2324)
    - Dupointe, Mary T. Hutnak, 1954 (Box 215, Folder 2325)
    - Dupont, Henry, Jr., 1955 (Box 215, Folder 2326)
    - Dupont, Raoul, 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2327)
    - Duponte, Francis M., 1952 (Box 215, Folder 2328)
    - Dupras, Eleanor Brown, 1941 (Box 215, Folder 2329)
    - Dupras, Pierre, 1950 (Box 215, Folder 2330)
    - Dupre, Zoel, 1956 (Box 215, Folder 2331)
    - Duprey, Blanche J., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2332)
    - Duprey, Charles R., 1955 (Box 215, Folder 2333)
    - Duprey, Joseph A., 1952 (Box 215, Folder 2334)
    - Duprey, Lola K., 1940 (Box 215, Folder 2335)
    - Duprey, Rose L., 1939 (Box 215, Folder 2336)
    - Dupuis, Celia, 1950 (Box 215, Folder 2337)
    - Dupuis, George A., 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2338)
    - Dupuis, Joseph A., 1938 (Box 215, Folder 2339)
    - Dupuis, William F., 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2340)
    - Duquette, Arsene, 1956 (Box 215, Folder 2341)
    - Durand, Emelia (Mayhew, Amelia B.), 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2342)
    - Durand, Robert, 1955 (Box 215, Folder 2343)
    - Durocher, Alfred, 1949 (Box 215, Folder 2344)
    - Durocher, Lillian D., 1944 (Box 215, Folder 2345)
    - Durocher, Roland B., 1950 (Box 215, Folder 2346)
    - Duso, Aldor, 1952 (Box 215, Folder 2347)
    - Dussart, Raymond, 1949 (Box 215, Folder 2348)
    - Dusseault, Adelard J., 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2349)
    - Dusseault, Florence M., 1940 (Box 215, Folder 2350)
    - Dusseault, Joseph E., 1940 (Box 215, Folder 2351)
    - Dusseault, Napoleon J., 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2352)
    - Dusseault, Norman, 1939 (Box 215, Folder 2353)
    - Duthrie, Jesse J., 1946 (Box 215, Folder 2354)
    - Dutremble, Victor, 1953 (Box 215, Folder 2355)
    - Duval, Albertine M. P., 1956 (Box 215, Folder 2356)
    - Duval, Alexandre, 1940 (Box 215, Folder 2357)
    - Duval, Aurore, 1948 (Box 215, Folder 2358)
    - Duval, Celilia L., 1946 (Box 215, Folder 2359)
    - Duval, Edward J., 19 (Box 215, Folder 2360)
    - Duval, Evelyn Goven, 1944 (Box 215, Folder 2361)
    - Duval, George R., 1938 (Box 215, Folder 2362)
    - Duval, Gerard A., 1938 (Box 215, Folder 2363)
    - Duval, Napoleon J., 1957 (Box 215, Folder 2364)
    - Duval, Romeo, Jr., 1955 (Box 215, Folder 2365)
    - Dvarcas, Ardella M. M., 1948 (Box 215, Folder 2366)
    - Dyson, Joseph, 1938 (Box 215, Folder 2367)
    - Dziedzic, Steffenia Witalec, 1939 (Box 215, Folder 2368)
    - Dziedzic, Walter, 1939 (Box 215, Folder 2369)
    - Dziedzic, William J., 1940 (Box 215, Folder 2370)
    - Dzuban, Jessie M., 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2371)
    - Eastham, E. Louise, 1951 (Box 215, Folder 2372)
    - Edgar, Edward E., Jr., 1955 (Box 215, Folder 2373)
    - Edmondson, Bernice, 1946 (Box 215, Folder 2374)
    - Edmondson, Ivy H., 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2375)
    - Edmondson, William H., 1947 (Box 215, Folder 2376)
    - Edwards, Ralph, 1953 (Box 215, Folder 2377)
    - Effinger, Eugene, 1952 (Box 215, Folder 2378)
    - Egan, Alice, 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2379)
    - Egan, Ambrose, 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2380)
    - Egan, Loretta, 1957 (Box 215, Folder 2381)
    - Egan, Mary, 1945 (Box 215, Folder 2382)
    - Egan, Norman, 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2383)
    - Egan, Rose, 1955 (Box 215, Folder 2384)
    - Ellison, Thomas, 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2385)
    - Ellsworth, Walter, 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2386)
    - Emond, Lillian B., 1944 (Box 215, Folder 2387)
    - Engel, Edna, 1951 (Box 215, Folder 2388)
    - Engel, Joan, 1952 (Box 215, Folder 2389)
    - Ennis, Mary, 1941 (Box 215, Folder 2390)
    - Ennis, Pauline I., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2391)
    - Eno, Albert, 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2392)
    - Eno, Edward, 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2393)
    - Eno, John Edward, 1941 (Box 215, Folder 2394)
    - Espinosa, Anna, 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2395)
    - Espinosa, Fred, 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2396)
    - Espinosa, George, 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2397)
    - Espinosa, Michael A., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2398)
    - Espinosa, Robert, 1941 (Box 215, Folder 2399)
    - Etheridge, George, 1951 (Box 215, Folder 2400)
    - Etheridge, Gertrude, 1955 (Box 215, Folder 2401)
    - Ethier, Arlevine M., 1940 (Box 215, Folder 2402)
    - ethier, Mary Jane, 1956 (Box 215, Folder 2403)
    - Ethier, Maxim E., 1940 (Box 215, Folder 2404)
    - Evans, Morris, 1946 (Box 215, Folder 2405)
    - Eveshowsky, Stanley, 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2406)
    - Eyers, Roy E., 1953 (Box 215, Folder 2407)
    - Ezzell, Almond, 1956 (Box 215, Folder 2408)
    - Ezzell, Earl, 1955 (Box 215, Folder 2409)
    - Faber, John, 1946 (Box 215, Folder 2410)
    - Fafard, Rose F., 1941 (Box 215, Folder 2411)
    - Faille, Alfred J., 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2412)
    - Farland, Dow, 1953 (Box 215, Folder 2413)
    - Farland, Eugene, 1956 (Box 215, Folder 2414)
    - Farland, Flora L., 1954 (Box 215, Folder 2415)
    - Farland, Gordon, 1951 (Box 215, Folder 2416)
    - Farley, Leon, 1950 (Box 215, Folder 2417)
    - Farrell, Edward, 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2418)
    - Farrell, John J., Jr., 1952 (Box 215, Folder 2419)
    - Fenner, Earl, 1952 (Box 215, Folder 2420)
    - Ferguson, John, 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2421)
    - Ferreira, Jack, 1946 (Box 215, Folder 2422)
    - Ferreira, Joaquim, Jr., 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2423)
    - Ferreira, Manuel, 1946 (Box 215, Folder 2424)
    - Ferreira, Mary C., 1957 (Box 215, Folder 2425)
    - Fesik, Mary, 1938 (Box 215, Folder 2426)
    - Field, Donald, 1954 (Box 215, Folder 2427)
    - Field, Henry S., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2428)
    - Field, Juanita C., 1945 (Box 215, Folder 2429)
    - Fields, Walter A., 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2430)
    - Filiatreault, Agnes M., 1939 (Box 215, Folder 2431)
    - Filiatreault, Aurore D., 1939 (Box 215, Folder 2432)
    - Filiatreault, Clara A., 1940 (Box 215, Folder 2433)
    - Filkins, Kenneth H., 1938 (Box 215, Folder 2434)
    - Filkins, Marjorie K., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2435)
    - Filteau, Anna C., 1941 (Box 215, Folder 2436)
    - Filteau, Arthur A., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 24378)
    - Filteau, Gerard J., 1948 (Box 215, Folder 2438)
    - Filteau, Louis J., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2439)
    - Filteau, Louis J. H., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2440)
    - Filteau, Lucien J., 1957 (Box 215, Folder 2441)
    - Filteau, Viola, 1957 (Box 215, Folder 2442)
    - Finley, Irving, Jr., 1946 (Box 215, Folder 2443)
    - Fisher, Clement James, 1947 (Box 215, Folder 2444)
    - Fisher, Rita, 1947 (Box 215, Folder 2445)
    - Fisher, Roy, 1952 (Box 215, Folder 2446)
    - Fitzgerald, Catherine, 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2447)
    - Fitzmorris, Catherine, 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2448)
    - Flagg, Felix, 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2449)
    - Flagg, Louis C., 1939 (Box 215, Folder 2450)
    - Flanagan, Mary G., 1939 (Box 215, Folder 2451)
    - Flanagan, Margaret, 1939 (Box 215, Folder 2452)
    - Fleury, Alphonse, 1950 (Box 215, Folder 2453)
    - Fleury, Christine, 1948 (Box 215, Folder 2454)
    - Fleury, Joseph F., 1947 (Box 215, Folder 2455)
    - Flood, James F., 1951 (Box 215, Folder 2456)
    - Florence, Richard E., 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2457)
    - Flugel, Charles J., Jr., 1938 (Box 215, Folder 2458)
    - Flugel, Charles J., Sr., 1947 (Box 215, Folder 2459)
    - Flugel, Mary, 1953 (Box 215, Folder 2460)
    - Fontaine, Francis R., 1952 (Box 215, Folder 2461)
    - Fontaine, Henry, 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2462)
    - Fontaine, Joseph D., 1948 (Box 215, Folder 2463)
    - Fontaine, Lillian, 1951 (Box 215, Folder 2464)
    - Fontaine, Louis J., Jr., 1952 (Box 215, Folder 2465)
    - Fontaine, Raymond J., 1940 (Box 215, Folder 2466)
    - Ford, Edward Louis, Jr., 1953 (Box 215, Folder 2467)
    - Forest, Joseph A., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2468)
    - Fortin, Alderic, 1953 (Box 215, Folder 2469)
    - Fortin, Beatrice Piche, 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2470)
    - Fortin, Julia, 1953 (Box 215, Folder 2471)
    - Fortin, Marie Louise, 1946 (Box 215, Folder 2472)
    - Fortin, Nelson J., 1940 (Box 215, Folder 2473)
    - Fortin, Stella, 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2474)
    - Fortin, Zephren J., 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2475)
    - Foster, Rozilda, 1945 (Box 215, Folder 2476)
    - Fountain, Hector, 1941 (Box 215, Folder 2477)
    - Fountain, Lillian A., 1941 (Box 215, Folder 2478)
    - Fountaine, Joseph, 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2479)
    - Fournier, Alban E., 1943 (Box 215, Folder 2480)
    - Fournier, Amelia, 1950 (Box 215, Folder 2481)
    - Fournier, Bertha, 1951 (Box 215, Folder 2482)
    - Fournier, Claire A. G., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2483)
    - Fournier, Donat O., 1954 (Box 215, Folder 2484)
    - Fournier, Eva B. B., 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2485)
    - Fournier, Gertrude D., 1942 (Box 215, Folder 2486)
    - Fournier, Grace F. P., 1955 (Box 215, Folder 2487)
    - Fournier, Joseph, 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2488)
    - Fournier, Leo, 1951 (Box 215, Folder 2489)
    - Fournier, Leona, 1957 (Box 215, Folder 2490)
    - Fournier, Montcalm H., 1944 (Box 215, Folder 2491)
    - Fournier, Yvette B. B., 1937 (Box 215, Folder 2492)
    - Francis, John, 1956 (Box 216, Folder 2493)
    - Franklin, Charles, 1952 (Box 216, Folder 2464)
    - Franklin, William M., 1937 (Box 216, Folder 2495)
    - Frechette, Alice, 1945 (Box 216, Folder 2496)
    - Frechette, Arthur, 1947 (Box 216, Folder 2497)
    - Frechette, Beatrice C., 1941 (Box 216, Folder 2498)
    - Frechette, Flora E., 1939 (Box 216, Folder 2499)
    - Frechette, Gabriel A., 1952 (Box 216, Folder 2500)
    - Frechette, Hazel, 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2501)
    - Frechette, Henry J., 1950 (Box 216, Folder 2502)
    - Frechette, Jean Henry, 1955 (Box 216, Folder 2503)
    - Frechette, Joseph A., 1941 (Box 216, Folder 2504)
    - Frechette, Leo A., 1938 (Box 216, Folder 2505)
    - Frechette, Louis W., 1939 (Box 216, Folder 2506)
    - Frechette, Noel, 1943 (Box 216, Folder 2507)
    - Frechette, Noella G., 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2508)
    - Frechette, Norman, 1956 (Box 216, Folder 2509)
    - Frechette, Omer Joseph, 1943 (Box 216, Folder 2510)
    - Frechette, Oscar, 1943 (Box 216, Folder 2511)
    - Frechette, Rene, 1955 (Box 216, Folder 2512)
    - Frechette, Rene, 1956 (Box 216, Folder 2513)
    - Frechette, Simeon, 1956 (Box 216, Folder 251)
    - Frechette, Sylvia B., 1954 (Box 216, Folder 2515)
    - Fredette, Arthur J., 1937 (Box 216, Folder 2516)
    - Freeman, Maria M. N., 1943 (Box 216, Folder 2517)
    - Fregeau, Rita, 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2518)
    - French, Joseph, 1950 (Box 216, Folder 2519)
    - Frenette, Beatrice, 1943 (Box 216, Folder 2520)
    - Freniere, Earl H., 1940 (Box 216, Folder 2521)
    - Friese, August, Sr., 1948 (Box 216, Folder 2522)
    - Fuller, Olin, 1955 (Box 216, Folder 2523)
    - Gabler, Virginia, 1945 (Box 216, Folder 2524)
    - Gadreau, Albert, 1940 (Box 216, Folder 2525)
    - Gagne, Augustin, 1937 (Box 216, Folder 2526)
    - Gagne, Beatrice, 1956 (Box 216, Folder 2527)
    - Gagne, Charles, 1940 (Box 216, Folder 2528)
    - Gagne, Leo J., Jr., 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2529)
    - Gagne, Lucien, 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2530)
    - Gagnon, Adrien J., 1937 (Box 216, Folder 2531)
    - Gagnon, Alpherie, 1952 (Box 216, Folder 2532)
    - Gagnon, Antoine P., 1950 (Box 216, Folder 2533)
    - Gagnon, Archie J., 1952 (Box 216, Folder 2534)
    - Gagnon, Aurelie C., 1952 (Box 216, Folder 2535)
    - Gagnon, Blanche, 1950 (Box 216, Folder 2536)
    - Gagnon, Daniel, 1955 (Box 216, Folder 2537)
    - Gagnon, David A., 1948 (Box 216, Folder 2538)
    - Gagnon, Edward, 1941 (Box 216, Folder 2539)
    - Gagnon, Ephriam J., 1937 (Box 216, Folder 2540)
    - Gagnon, Ernestine R. A., 1943 (Box 216, Folder 2541)
    - Gagnon, Estelle C., 1953 (Box 216, Folder 2542)
    - Gagnon, Frances M., 1946 (Box 216, Folder 2543)
    - Gagnon, Henry, 1955 (Box 216, Folder 2544)
    - Ganon, Henry, 1939 (Box 216, Folder 2545)
    - Gagnon, John B., 1942 (Box 216, Folder 2546)
    - Gagnon, Joseph, 1948 (Box 216, Folder 2547)